So let's talk about earning in health insurance here.
Whenever you sell a policy in health insurance, you will
earn from 15% to 40%.
On first year and life long renewal, you will get
commission on 15% plus domestic and
international trip which is additional and
free of cost.
[Music]
Fully
[Prasha]
Today I am going to talk to you about
why you should become an agent of ICC Lord's.
What are the benefits of becoming an agent here, how much money you
can earn, in what ways you
can sell insurance, I will share all the knowledge with
you in working here. There are some
mandatory conditions, I will also tell you about them. My
name is Yogendra Verma, I am ICSC Lombard
Recruitment Manager and friends, keep in mind that it is
very important to watch this video till the end, only then
you will understand all the terms and conditions
clearly. Those who have
come to the channel for the first time, it is important to subscribe to the channel,
share it, comment on it and click on the bell icon, only then
you will keep getting all the financial updates. So quickly
friends, I am talking to all those people who are doing
their job, business and professional life.  Are you
unemployed with any activity
or are you a housewife and
you feel that you are looking for some side by side
part time earning source,
then I finish your source, your working here, I
provide you the option of an agency of ICC Lord in
which you can do health insurance,
motor insurance and non-motor
insurance working, this is such a
big company, such a great profile in
which lakhs and crores of rupees can be easily
earned, friends, even if you are a
fresher, you may
not know the ABC of insurance,
but if you have the skill to learn,
if you want to learn something in life,
want to earn big money, then there is
no age limit for learning, you
can learn at any age and
we have the full responsibility of teaching, friends, those who will
become agents in ICC Lord, let me
tell you what work they have to do, they can sell health insurance on all over India basis, they
can do motor insurance of all vehicles
and non-motor insurance, this is a
very big profile, three things with a single code
You can do all kinds of work here and earn a
lot.
Learning is available here on a part-time basis.
Full-time learning is available on this. You will be
able to do all this work easily along with your job and business. All this training knowledge is done
through Zoom meetings. You just have to
give learning and training with us.
We guide you in all this learning. There is a
proper
support system from the company and we also
provide genuine training from our side
so that your learning and grooming happens
very well. So let's talk about
earning in health insurance here.
Whenever you
sell a policy in health insurance, you will get earning from 15% to 40%. You will get
commission on life long 15% on the first year and renewal.
Plus you will get domestic and international trips
which are additionally free of cost.
You will use fully luxury treatment
and tension free. This is a very big and amazing
thing. The second option you will get is to do
motor insurance but
you will be able to work in motor insurance only
when the code comes.  Later, in the first month, you will
login for a health policy worth Rs. 15,000.
If you do not login for any health policy
and
want to get Lombard code only for motor insurance, then I am sorry,
we do not provide the code. Please keep in mind
that we are
associated with the health insurance team, so our
main purpose is to teach you health insurance and to teach you how to
sell it. So, it will be necessary to do health insurance.
Minimum four policies in a year
and one policy in the first month, only then you will be
able to do motor and non-motor insurance work. You have to take
special care of this working, this
is a mandatory condition. No matter where you are in India, you
can get ready for this working, you can join
and there is nothing tough in it. There will be a very simple
small IRDA exam
for which a fee of ₹1 will be charged. This fee is a one-time
fee. Once you pass the exam,
you will not have to pay any money after that for the rest of your life.
We will share its entire learning material etc. with you. You will have to
go to the exam center for one hour, located
in your nearby location.  Exam center is
available, we will share all that knowledge working with you.
Now let me talk to you
why you should join ICC Lombard, so you should
join IC Lombard because it is
one of the best and wonderful company,
friends, claim settlement is hassle free here,
most network hospitals
are covered with the company and the customer gets hassle free policies, tension
free policies,
whether you
sell health insurance, motor insurance or
non-motor insurance, the
customer remains relaxed for all, appreciates you
and by associating with a good brand,
your value will also be added, people will also
recognize you and somewhere or the other,
extra earning will come to your house too. You will get this
best part only by
joining IC Lombard. Those who want to
start this journey in IC Lombard,
want to join this working
and
want to earn active as well as passive income throughout their life, then you should
whatsapp us. How to become IC Lombard, I will give you the entire list
of documents which is given here on the side, you should give
me all these lists of documents.  You will have to
pay the examination fee of WhatsApp2
and after that I will have a virtual interaction with you, only
after that we will process your code, it will take
a week to 10 days for this
process and
as soon as your exam is over within 10 days,
you can start working after passing the exam and
I am telling you again that this is a complete digital
platform, no matter in which corner of India you are,
Goa, West Bengal,
UP, Madras or Jalandhar, Punjab, anywhere, the
exam is available everywhere and
after passing the exam there is
no need to go to any branch,
we teach you to do all the work online
through zoom meeting, you should be absolutely worry-free for that,
we will share the entire knowledge training with you,
Namaskar, your friend Yogendra
Brahman
[Music]